Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Trust for New Music Records, 1996-2011
State University of New York at Buffalo, Music Library
- 2002, VIII.; Item 2002-001-2002-133
  - Individual applications, 2002, C.; Item 2002-08-2002-039
    - Troy, T.J. (Box 43, Item 2002-037)
    - Van Brink, Matthew (Box 43, Item 2002-038)
    - Zimmerman, Antonio (Box 43, Item 2002-039)
  - Organization applications, 2002, D.; Item 2002-040-2002-074
    - Aldeburgh Productions (Box 43, Item 2002-040)
    - Alliance of Michigan State University Composers (Box 43, Item 2002-041)
    - Atlantic Brass Quintet (Box 43, Item 2002-042)
    - Cantori New York (Box 43, Item 2002-043)
    - Common Sense Composers' Collective (Box 43, Item 2002-044)
    - Composers Guild of New Jersey (Box 44, Item 2002-045)
    - Copland House (Box 44, Item 2002-046)
    - CUBE Contemporary Chamber Ensemble (Box 44, Item 2002-047)
    - Cygnus Ensemble (Box 44, Item 2002-048)
    - Czech-American Summer Music Institute (Box 44, Item 2002-049)
    - Downtown Music Productions (Box 44, Item 2002-050)
    - Empyrean Ensemble (Box 44, Item 2002-051)
    - Ensemble Aleph (Box 44, Item 2002-052)
    - Experimental Intermedia (Box 44, Item 2002-053)
    - Fear No Music (Box 44, Item 2002-054)
    - LAMPO (Box 44, Item 2002-055)
    - League of Composers/ISCM (Box 44, Item 2002-056)
    - Locrian Chamber Players (Box 44, Item 2002-057)
    - London Sinfonietta (Box 44, Item 2002-058)
    - Meridian Gallery (Box 44, Item 2002-059)
    - Merkin Concert Hall (Box 44, Item 2002-060)
    - New Albion Records (Box 44, Item 2002-061)
    - New Century Saxophone Quartet (Box 44, Item 2002-062)
    - New York Virtuoso Singers (Box 44, Item 2002-063)
    - North/South Consonance (Box 45, Item 2002-064)
    - Northwestern University (Box 45, Item 2002-065)
    - Paul Dresher Ensemble (Box 45, Item 2002-066)
    - Pekarsky Percussion Ensemble (Box 45, Item 2002-067)
    - Performing Arts Chicago (Box 45, Item 2002-068)
    - Roulette (Box 45, Item 2002-069)
    - San Diego New Music (Box 45, Item 2002-070)
    - Society for New Music (Box 45, Item 2002-071)
    - The Culture Project (Box 45, Item 2002-072)
    - The Walden School (Box 45, Item 2002-073)
    - Zeitgeist (Musical group) (Box 45, Item 2002-074)
  - Audio recordings, 2002, E.; Item 2002-075-2002-076
    - Bahr, Jason (Box 46, Item 2002-075)
    - Bisesi, Jonathan (Box 46, Item 2002-076)
    - Bisesi, Jonathan (Box 46, Item 2002-077)
    - Carrasco, Laura (Box 46, Item 2002-078)
    - Cassidy, Aaron (Box 46, Item 2002-079)
    - Choi, Denise (Box 46, Item 2002-080)
    - Choi, Denise (Box 46, Item 2002-081)
    - Choi, Winston (Box 46, Item 2002-082)
    - Coleman, Dan (Box 46, Item 2002-083)
    - Esler, Robert (Box 46, Item 2002-084)
    - Feeney, Timothy (Box 46, Item 2002-085)
    - Frank, Gabriela Lena (Box 46, Item 2002-086)
    - Gee, Erin (Box 46, Item 2002-087)
    - Grossman, Jorge (Box 46, Item 2002-088)
    - Hallman, Joseph (Box 46, Item 2002-089)
    - Kim, Suk-Jun (Box 46, Item 2002-090)
    - Lan, Mei-mi (Box 46, Item 2002-091)
    - Lin, Mei-Fang (Box 46, Item 2002-092)
    - Mastrian, Stacey Lynn (Box 46, Item 2002-093)
    - Melland, Justin Joseph (Box 46, Item 2002-094)
    - Montanaro, Larisa (Box 46, Item 2002-095)
    - Myers, Jeff (Box 46, Item 2002-096)
    - Notareschi, Loretta (Box 46, Item 2002-097)
    - Ruo, Huang (Box 46, Item 2002-098)
    - Rutherford, John (Box 46, Item 2002-099)
    - Saoud, Erick (Box 46, Item 2002-100)
    - Saulle, Joshua (Box 46, Item 2002-101)
    - Tignor, Scott (Box 46, Item 2002-102)
    - Troy, T.J. (Box 46, Item 2002-103)
    - Troy, T.J. (Box 46, Item 2002-104)
    - Valdes, Cristina (Box 46, Item 2002-105)
    - Valdes, Cristina (Box 47, Item 2002-106)
    - Van Brink, Matthew (Box 47, Item 2002-107)
    - Zimmerman, Antonio (Box 47, Item 2002-108)
    - Alliance of Michigan State University Composers (Box 47, Item 2002-109)
    - Atlantic Brass Quintet (Box 47, Item 2002-110)
    - Atlantic Brass Quintet (Box 47, Item 2002-111)
    - Cantori New York (Box 47, Item 2002-112)
    - Composers Guild of New Jersey (Box 47, Item 2002-113)
    - Concerts M (Box 47, Item 2002-113a)
    - Copland House (Box 47, Item 2002-114)
    - CUBE Contemporary Chamber Ensemble (Box 47, Item 2002-115)
    - Ensemble Aleph (Box 47, Item 2002-116)
    - Ensemble Aleph (Box 47, Item 2002-117)
    - Experimental Intermedia (Box 47, Item 2002-118)
    - Empyrean Ensemble (Box 47, Item 2002-119)
    - Experimental Intermedia (Box 47, Item 2002-120)
    - Locrian Chamber Players (Box 47, Item 2002-121)
    - Locrian Chamber Players (Box 47, Item 2002-122)
    - Merkin Concert Hall (Meridian Ensemble) (Box 47, Item 2002-123)
    - North/South Consonance (Box 47, Item 2002-124)
    - North/South Consonance (Box 47, Item 2002-125)
    - Performing Arts Chicago (Box 47, Item 2002-126)
    - Paul Dresher Ensemble (Box 47, Item 2002-127)
    - Pekarsky Percussion Ensemble (Box 47, Item 2002-128)
    - San Diego New Music (Box 47, Item 2002-129)
    - Society for New Music (Box 47, Item 2002-130)
    - Zeitgeist (Box 47, Item 2002-131)
  - Scores, 2002, F.; Item 2002-132-2002-133
    - Hallman, Joseph Cancione, 1999, 1 ms. score (40 p.); 28 cm. (Box 80, Item 2002-132)
      For voice and piano.
    - Hallman, Joseph Handfuls: 11 songs after poems by Carl Sandburg, 1999, 1 score (18 p.); 22 x 36 cm. (Box 80, Item 2002-133)
      For mezzo-soprano and piano.
- 2003, IX.; Item 2003-001-2003-102
  - Individual award recipients, 2003, A.; Item 2003-001-2003-002
    - Norsworthy, Michael (Box 48, Item 2003-001)
    - Ramirez, Catherine (Box 48, Item 2003-002)
  - Organization award recipients, 2003, B.; Item 2003-003
    - Experimental Intermedia (Box 48, Item 2003-003a)
    - Northwestern University School of Music (Box 48, Item 2008-003b)
    - Zeitgeist (Musical group) (Box 48, Item 2003-003c)
  - Individual applications, 2003, C.; Item 2003-004-2003-16
    - Carrasco, Laura (Box 48, Item 2003-004)
    - Fitisova, Varvara (Box 48, Item 2003-005)
    - Gee, Erin (Box 48, Item 2003-006)
    - Harder, Lane (Box 48, Item 2003-007)
    - Hsu, Olen (Box 48, Item 2003-008)
    - Huang, Aiyun (Box 48, Item 2003-009)
    - Kajcienski, Matthew (Box 48, Item 2003-010)
    - Lam, Angel (Box 48, Item 2003-011)
    - Lin, Jenny (Box 48, Item 2003-012)
    - Lopez, Jairo Duarte (Box 48, Item 2003-013)
    - Penman, Joshua (Box 48, Item 2003-014)
    - Steinhoff, Anna (Box 48, Item 2003-015)
    - Stockton, Geoffrey (Box 48, Item 2003-016)
  - Organization applications, 2003, D.; Item 2003-017-2003-061
    - 3rd Angle (Box 48, Item 2003-017)
    - Albany Symphony Orchestra (Box 48, Item 2003-018)
    - Aldeburgh Productions (Box 49, Item 2003-019)
    - American Baroque (Box 49, Item 2003-020)
    - Auros Group for New Music (Box 49, Item 2003-021)
    - The Barton Workshop (Box 49, Item 2003-022)
    - Bridge Records (Box 49, Item 2003-023)
    - CEAMC (Box 49, Item 2003-024)
    - The Chicago Classical Recording Foundation (Box 49, Item 2003-025)
    - Citywinds/Intersection (Box 49, Item 2003-026)
    - Common Sense Composers' Collective (Box 49, Item 2003-027)
    - Composers Guild of New Jersey (Box 49, Item 2003-028)
    - Copland House (Box 49, Item 2003-029)
    - Cygnus Ensemble (Box 49, Item 2003-030)
    - Czech-American Summer Music Institute (Box 49, Item 2003-031)
    - Da Capo Chamber Players (Box 49, Item 2003-032)
    - Electronic Music Foundation (Box 50, Item 2003-033)
    - Esoterics (Box 50, Item 2003-034)
    - Essential Music (Musical group) (Box 50, Item 2003-035)
    - House Foundation for the Arts (Box 50, Item 2003-036)
    - LAMPO (Box 50, Item 2003-037)
    - Locrian Chamber Players (Box 50, Item 2003-038)
    - London Sinfonietta (Box 50, Item 2003-039)
    - Mendelssohn Club (Box 50, Item 2003-040)
    - Meridian Gallery (Box 50, Item 2003-041)
    - Minimum Security Composers Collective (Box 50, Item 2003-042)
    - New Century Saxophone Quartet (Box 50, Item 2003-043)
    - New World Records/Anderson (Box 50, Item 2003-044)
    - New World Records/Cassatt (Box 50, Item 2003-045)
    - New World Records/Coleman (Box 50, Item 2003-046)
    - New York Treble Singers (Box 50, Item 2003-047)
    - New York Virtuoso Singers (Box 50, Item 2003-048)
    - North/South Consonance (Box 51, Item 2003-049)
    - Old Dominion University (Box 51, Item 2003-050)
    - Other Minds (Box 51, Item 2003-051)
    - Relache Ensemble (Box 51, Item 2003-052)
    - Roulette (Box 51, Item 2003-053)
    - ROVA Arts (Box 51, Item 2003-054)
    - San Francisco Chamber Singers (Box 51, Item 2003-055)
    - San Francisco Contemporary Music Players (Box 51, Item 2003-056)
    - Santa Fe New Music (Box 51, Item 2003-057)
    - Society for New Music (Box 51, Item 2003-058)
    - Tampa Bay Composers' Forum (Box 51, Item 2003-059)
    - VCME (Box 51, Item 2003-060)
    - The Walden School (Box 51, Item 2003-061)
  - Audio recordings, 2003, E.; Item 2003-062-2003-102
    - Carrasco, Laura (Box 52, Item 2003-062)
    - Fitisova, Varvara (Box 52, Item 2003-063)
    - Gee, Erin (Box 52, Item 2003-064)
    - Harder, Lane (Box 52, Item 2003-065)
    - Huang, Aiyun (Box 52, Item 2003-066)
    - Kajcienski, Matthew (Box 52, Item 2003-067)
    - Lam, Angel (Box 52, Item 2003-068)
    - Lin, Jenny (Box 52, Item 2003-069)
    - Lopez, Jairo Duarte (Box 52, Item 2003-070)
    - Norsworthy, Michael (Box 52, Item 2003-071)
    - Penman, Joshua (Box 52, Item 2003-072)
    - Steinhoff, Anna (Box 52, Item 2003-073)
    - 3rd Angle (Box 52, Item 2003-074)
    - Albany Symphony Orchestra (Box 52, Item 2003-075)
    - Auros Group for New Music (Box 52, Item 2003-076)
    - Bridge Records (Box 52, Item 2003-077)
    - Bridge Records (Box 52, Item 2003-078)
    - Citywinds/Intersection (Box 52, Item 2003-079)
    - Composers Guild of New Jersey (Box 52, Item 2003-080)
    - Cygnus Ensemble (Box 52, Item 2003-081)
    - Cygnus Ensemble (Box 52, Item 2003-082)
    - Essential Music (Musical group) (Box 52, Item 2003-083)
    - Experimental Intermedia (Box 52, Item 2003-083a)
    - Locrian Chamber Players (Box 53, Item 2003-084)
    - London Sinfonietta (Box 53, Item 2003-085)
    - New York Treble Singers (Box 53, Item 2003-086)
    - Meridian Gallery (Box 53, Item 2003-087)
    - Minimum Security Composers Collective (Box 53, Item 2003-088)
    - New World Records/Anderson (Box 53, Item 2003-089)
    - New World Records/Cassatt (Box 53, Item 2003-090)
    - New World Records/Coleman (Box 53, Item 2003-091)
    - North/South Consonance (Box 53, Item 2003-092)
    - Old Dominion University (Box 53, Item 2003-093)
    - Relache Ensemble (Box 53, Item 2003-094)
    - Other Minds (Box 53, Item 2003-095)
    - San Francisco Chamber Singers (Box 53, Item 2003-096)
    - San Francisco Contemporary Music Players (Box 53, Item 2003-097)
    - Santa Fe New Music (Box 53, Item 2003-098)
    - Society for New Music (Box 53, Item 2003-099)
    - Society for New Music (Box 53, Item 2003-100)
    - VCME (Box 53, Item 2003-101)
    - Zeitgeist (Box 53, Item 2003-102)
- 2004, X.; Item 2004-001-2004-153
  - Individual award recipients, 2004, A.; Item 2004-001-2004-002
    - Petraskevics, Janis (Box 54, Item 2004-001)
    - Solomon, Samuel (Box 54, Item 2004-002)
  - Organization award recipients, 2004, B.; Item 2004-003-2004-006
    - Empyrean Ensemble (Box 54, Item 2004-003)
    - Living Artist Recordings (Box 54, Item 2004-004)
    - London Sinfonietta (Box 54, Item 2004-005)
    - November Music Festival (Box 54, Item 2004-006)
  - Individual applications, 2004, C.; Item 2004-007-2004-037
    - Amon, Jonathan (Box 54, Item 2004-007)
    - Bauer, Randall (Box 54, Item 2004-008)
    - Blocker, Jesse (Box 54, Item 2004-009)
    - Bloland, Per (Box 54, Item 2004-010)
    - Cahn-Lipman, Kivie (Box 54, Item 2004-011)
    - Callahan, Moiya (Box 54, Item 2004-012)
    - Clayton, April (Box 54, Item 2004-013)
    - Crossland, Patrick (Box 54, Item 2004-014)
    - Daniel, Marlon (Box 54, Item 2004-015)
    - Davis, Nathan (Box 54, Item 2004-016)
    - Deng, Haiqiong (Box 54, Item 2004-017)
    - Feeney, Timothy (Box 54, Item 2004-018)
    - Feltman, Joshua (Box 54, Item 2004-019)
    - Fitzgerald, Jennifer (Box 54, Item 2004-020)
    - Gerstein, Ben (Box 54, Item 2004-021)
    - Hagen, Lars Petter (Box 54, Item 2004-022)
    - Hong, Sung Joo (Box 55, Item 2004-023)
    - Kallenberg, Haley (Box 55, Item 2004-024)
    - Kaplan, Leonel (Box 55, Item 2004-025)
    - Kim, Ha-Yang (Box 55, Item 2004-026)
    - Lee, Damon (Box 55, Item 2004-027)
    - Lee, Wendy (Box 55, Item 2004-028)
    - Lippel, Daniel (Box 55, Item 2004-029)
    - Mallonee, Caroline (Box 55, Item 2004-030)
    - Merhavi, Ron (Box 55, Item 2004-031)
    - Moses, Laurie Lee (Box 55, Item 2004-032)
    - Nagai, Michelle (Box 55, Item 2004-033)
    - Pieslak, Jonathan (Box 55, Item 2004-034)
    - Roginski, Raphael (Box 55, Item 2004-035)
    - Schmidt, Heather (Box 55, Item 2004-036)
    - Trinier, Kristy (Box 55, Item 2004-037)
  - Organization applications, 2004, D.; Item 2004-038-2004-084
    - Albany Symphony Orchestra (Box 55, Item 2004-038)
    - Albany Symphony Orchestra (Box 55, Item 2004-039)
    - American Composers Orchestra (Box 55, Item 2004-040)
    - Bonk Festival (Box 55, Item 2004-041)
    - Boston Microtonal Society (Box 55, Item 2004-042)
    - Boulder Youth Symphony Society (Box 55, Item 2004-043)
    - Bridge Records (Box 55, Item 2004-044)
    - California Institute of the Arts (Box 55, Item 2004-045)
    - Canisius College (Box 55, Item 2004-046)
    - Cedille Records (Box 56, Item 2004-047)
    - Chameleon Arts Ensemble of Boston (Box 56, Item 2004-048)
    - Citywinds (Musical group) (Box 56, Item 2004-049)
    - Composers in Red Sneakers (Box 56, Item 2004-050)
    - Continuum (Box 56, Item 2004-051)
    - CrossSound (Box 56, Item 2004-052)
    - Da Capo Chamber Players (Box 56, Item 2004-053)
    - Earplay (Musical group) (Box 56, Item 2004-054)
    - Electronic Music Foundation (Box 56, Item 2004-055)
    - Ensemble Sospeso (Box 56, Item 2004-056)
    - The Esoterics (Box 56, Item 2004-057)
    - Harpsichord Unlimited (Box 56, Item 2004-058)
    - House Foundation for the Arts (Box 56, Item 2004-059)
    - John D. Robb Musical Trust (Box 56, Item 2004-060)
    - Locrian Chamber Players (Box 57, Item 2004-061)
    - MATA (Box 57, Item 2004-062)
    - Minimum Security Composers Collective (Box 57, Item 2004-063)
    - Minnesota Orchestra (Box 57, Item 2004-064)
    - Modern Works (Box 57, Item 2004-065)
    - Network for New Music (Box 57, Item 2004-066)
    - New Century Saxophone Quartet (Box 57, Item 2004-067)
    - New Ear Contemporary Chamber Ensemble (Box 57, Item 2004-068)
    - New Music Bay Area (Box 57, Item 2004-069)
    - New York Treble Singers (Box 57, Item 2004-070)
    - New York Virtuoso Singers (Box 57, Item 2004-071)
    - Quatuor Molinari (Box 57, Item 2004-072)
    - Radius Ensemble (Box 58, Item 2004-073)
    - Relache Ensemble (Box 58, Item 2004-074)
    - Riverside Symphony (Box 58, Item 2004-075)
    - Roulette (Box 58, Item 2004-076)
    - Santa Fe New Music (Box 58, Item 2004-077)
    - School of Music, East Carolina University (Box 58, Item 2004-078)
    - Seal Bay Festival (Box 58, Item 2004-079)
    - Sequitur (Box 58, Item 2004-080)
    - Tzadik/Hips Road (Box 58, Item 2004-081)
    - University of Nebraska at Kearney (Box 58, Item 2004-082)
    - Utah State University (Box 58, Item 2004-083)
    - Voices of Change (Box 58, Item 2004-084)
  - Audio recordings, 2004, E.; Item 2004-085-2004-152
    - Amon, Jonathan (Box 59, Item 2004-085)
    - Bauer, Randall (Box 59, Item 2004-086)
    - Blocker, Jesse (Box 59, Item 2004-087)
    - Bloland, Per (Box 59, Item 2004-088)
    - Cahn-Lipman, Kivie (Box 59, Item 2004-089)
    - Callahan, Moiya (Box 59, Item 2004-090)
    - Clayton, April (Box 59, Item 2004-091)
    - Clayton, April (Box 59, Item 2004-092)
    - Clayton, April (Box 59, Item 2004-093)
    - Crossland, James (Box 59, Item 2004-094)
    - Daniel, Marlon (Box 59, Item 2004-095)
    - Davis, Nathan (Box 59, Item 2004-096)
    - Deng, Haiqiong (Box 59, Item 2004-097)
    - Feeney, Timothy (Box 59, Item 2004-098)
    - Feltman, Joshua (Box 59, Item 2004-099)
    - Fitzgerald, Jennifer (Box 59, Item 2004-100)
    - Gerstein, Ben (Box 59, Item 2004-101)
    - Hagen, Lars Petter (Box 59, Item 2004-102)
    - Hong, Sung Joo (Box 59, Item 2004-103)
    - Kallenberg, Haley (Box 59, Item 2004-104)
    - Kaplan, Leonel (Box 59, Item 2004-105)
    - Kim, Ha-Yang (Box 59, Item 2004-106)
    - Lee, Damon (Box 59, Item 2004-107)
    - Lee, Damon (Box 59, Item 2004-108)
    - Lippel, Daniel (Box 59, Item 2004-109)
    - Mallonee, Caroline (Box 59, Item 2004-110)
    - Merhavi, Ron (Box 59, Item 2004-111)
    - Nagai, Michelle (Box 59, Item 2004-112)
    - Petraskevics, Janis (Box 59, Item 2004-113)
    - Petraskevics, Janis (Box 59, Item 2004-114)
    - Pieslak, Jonathan (Box 59, Item 2004-115)
    - Roginski, Raphael (Box 59, Item 2004-116)
    - Schimdt, Heather (Box 59, Item 2004-117)
    - Solomon, Samuel (Box 59, Item 2004-118)
    - Trinier, Kristy (Box 60, Item 2004-119)
    - American Composers Orchestra (Box 60, Item 2004-120)
    - Boston Microtonal Society (Box 60, Item 2004-121)
    - Boulder Youth Symphony Society (Box 60, Item 2004-122)
    - Canisius College (Box 60, Item 2004-123)
    - Chameleon Arts Ensemble of Boston (Box 60, Item 2004-124)
    - Citywinds (Musical group) (Box 60, Item 2004-125)
    - Composers in Red Sneakers (Box 60, Item 2004-126)
    - Composers in Red Sneakers (Box 60, Item 2004-127)
    - Continuum (Box 60, Item 2004-128)
    - Continuum (Box 60, Item 2004-129)
    - Earplay (Musical group) (Box 60, Item 2004-130)
    - Earplay (Musical group) (Box 60, Item 2004-131)
    - Earplay (Musical group) (Box 60, Item 2004-132)
    - Empyrean Ensemble (Box 60, Item 2004-133)
    - The Ensemble Sospeso (Box 60, Item 2004-134)
    - Harpsichord Unlimited (Box 60, Item 2004-135)
    - Locrian Chamber Players (Box 60, Item 2004-136)
    - Minimum Security Composers Collective (Box 60, Item 2004-137)
    - New Ear Contemporary Chamber Ensemble (Box 60, Item 2004-138)
    - New Music Bay Area (Box 60, Item 2004-139)
    - New York New Music Ensemble (Box 60, Item 2004-140)
    - New York New Music Ensemble (Box 60, Item 2004-141)
    - New York Treble Singers (Box 60, Item 2004-142)
    - November Music (Box 60, Item 2004-143)
    - November Music (Box 60, Item 2004-144)
    - November Music (Box 60, Item 2004-145)
    - November Music (Box 60, Item 2004-146)
    - November Music (Box 60, Item 2004-147)
    - November Music (Box 60, Item 2004-148)
    - Radius Ensemble (Box 60, Item 2004-149)
    - Relache Ensemble (Box 60, Item 2004-150)
    - Santa Fe New Music (Box 60, Item 2004-151)
    - Utah State University (Box 60, Item 2004-152)
- 2005, XI.; Item 2005-001-2005-069
  - Individual award recipients, 2005, A.; Item 2005-001-2005-008
    - Haber, Yotam (Box 61, Item 2005-001)
    - Hanner, David (Box 61, Item 2005-002)
    - Holt, Danny (Box 61, Item 2005-003)
    - Johnson, Evan (Box 61, Item 2005-004)
    - Lippel, Daniel (Box 61, Item 2005-005)
    - Rosenboom, Daniel Aaron (Box 61, Item 2005-006)
    - Schotzko, David (Box 61, Item 2005-007)
    - Yitzhaki, Ofra (Box 61, Item 2005-008)
  - Organization award recipients, 2005, B.; 0 items
    There were no awards given to organizations in 2005.
  - Individual applications, 2005, C.; Item 2005-009-2005-032
    - Allison, Shawn (Box 61, Item 2005-009)
    - Aston, Stephanie (Box 61, Item 2005-010)
    - Brady, Sarah (Box 61, Item 2005-011)
    - Cahn-Lipman, Kivie (Box 61, Item 2005-012)
    - Callahan, Moiya (Box 61, Item 2005-013)
    - Diaz de Leon, Mario (Box 61, Item 2005-014)
    - Diller, Adam (Box 61, Item 2005-015)
    - DuRuz, James Vincent (Box 61, Item 2005-016)
    - Fallowfield, Ellen Harriet (Box 62, Item 2005-017)
    - Galvez-Troncher, Carlos (Box 62, Item 2005-018)
    - Homan, David (Box 62, Item 2005-019)
    - Hsu, Olen (Box 62, Item 2005-020)
    - Jacoby, Derek (Box 62, Item 2005-021)
    - Kendrick, Eva (Box 62, Item 2005-022)
    - Manthey, Robert (Box 62, Item 2005-023)
    - Mieloch, David (Box 62, Item 2005-024)
    - Milosavljevic, Ana (Box 62, Item 2005-025)
    - Orfe, John Christian (Box 62, Item 2005-026)
    - Sacawa, Brian (Box 62, Item 2005-027)
    - Shapiro, Daniel (Box 62, Item 2005-028)
    - Thudium, Heather (Box 62, Item 2005-029)
    - Wallace, Vita (Box 62, Item 2005-030)
    - Welch, Matthew (Box 62, Item 2005-031)
    - Wilcox, Stephen (Box 62, Item 2005-032)
  - Organization applications, 2005, D.; 0 items
    There were no applications received from organizations in 2005.
  - Audio recordings, 2005, E.; Item 2005-033-2005-069
    - Allison, Shawn (Box 63, Item 2005-033)
    - Aston, Stephanie (Box 63, Item 2005-034)
    - Brady, Sarah (Box 63, Item 2005-035)
    - Cahn-Lipman, Kivie (Box 63, Item 2005-036)
    - Callahan, Moiya (Box 63, Item 2005-037)
    - Diaz de Leon, Mario (Box 63, Item 2005-038)
    - Diller, Adam (Box 63, Item 2005-039)
    - DuRuz, James Vincent (Box 63, Item 2005-040)
    - Fallowfield, Ellen Harriet (Box 63, Item 2005-041)
    - Galvez-Troncher, Carlos (Box 63, Item 2005-042)
    - Galvez-Troncher, Carlos (Box 63, Item 2005-043)
    - Haber, Yotam (Box 63, Item 2005-044)
    - Hanner, David (Box 63, Item 2005-045)
    - Hanner, David (Box 63, Item 2005-046)
    - Holt, Danny (Box 63, Item 2005-047)
    - Homan, David (Box 63, Item 2005-048)
    - Homan, David (Box 63, Item 2005-049)
    - Jacoby, Derek (Box 63, Item 2005-050)
    - Johnson, Evan (Box 63, Item 2005-051)
    - Kendrick, Eva (Box 63, Item 2005-052)
    - Lippel, Daniel (Box 63, Item 2005-053)
    - Manthey, Robert (Box 63, Item 2005-054)
    - Mieloch, David (Box 63, Item 2005-055)
    - Rosenboom, Daniel Aaron (Box 63, Item 2005-056)
    - Rosenboom, Daniel Aaron (Box 63, Item 2005-057)
    - Sacawa, Brian (Box 63, Item 2005-058)
    - Sacawa, Brian (Box 63, Item 2005-059)
    - Schotzko, David (Box 63, Item 2005-060)
    - Shapiro, Daniel (Box 63, Item 2005-061)
    - Thudium, Heather (Box 63, Item 2005-062)
    - Wallace, Vita (Box 63, Item 2005-063)
    - Wallace, Vita (Box 63, Item 2005-064)
    - Welch, Matthew (Box 63, Item 2005-065)
    - Welch, Matthew (Box 63, Item 2005-066)
    - Wilcox, Stephen (Box 63, Item 2005-067)
    - Yitzhaki, Ofra (Box 63, Item 2005-068)
    - Yitzhaki, Ofra (Box 63, Item 2005-069)
- 2008, XII.; Item 2008-001-2008-260
  Arranged into four subseries:
  A. Award recipients
  B. Applicants (Pianist and Composer)
  C. Audio and video recordings
  D. Scores
  - Award recipients, 2008, A.; Item 2008-001-2008-003
    Arranged alphabetically by the pianist's last name..
    - Chang, Jihye, Johnson, Derek (Box 64, Item 2008-001)
    - Lin, Jenny, Freeman, Jason (Box 64, Item 2008-002)
    - O'Donnell, Heather, Imai, Shintaro (Box 64, Item 2008-003)
  - Applications (Pianist and Composer), 2008, B.; Item 2008-004-2008-049
    Arranged alphabetically by the pianist's last name.
    - Andres, Timothy, Muhly, Nico (Box 64, Item 2008-004)
    - Antoniadis, Pavlos, Minikakis, Stratis (Box 64, Item 2008-005)
    - Arnone, Augustus, Klingbeil, Michael (Box 64, Item 2008-006)
    - Barelos, Stacy, King, Mary (Box 64, Item 2008-007)
    - Barger, Laura, Schuessler, Philip (Box 64, Item 2008-008)
    - Bellheim, Markus, Lee, Damon (Box 64, Item 2008-009)
    - Bengston, Matthew, Berkowitz, Aaron (Box 64, Item 2008-010)
    - Bob, Sarah, Holland, Jonathan (Box 64, Item 2008-011)
    - Cheng, Amy I-Lin, Maloy, Kris (Box 64, Item 2008-012)
    - Croene, Frederik, Prins, Stefan (Box 64, Item 2008-013)
    - Ding, Shiau-uen, Huang, Tsai-Yun (Box 64, Item 2008-014)
    - Dudley, Sonia, Velingieri, Gianluca (Box 64, Item 2008-015)